

Oleh Taran

FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Contact

Y Kyiv, Ukraine



olehtarandev@gmail.com

☐ https://github.com/Lone1ynight

Skills

Javascript, Solidity

React

TypeScript

Node.js

Next.js

Nest.js

Redux (Toolkit, RTK Query)

TanStackQuery (useQuery)

Apollo Client

MaterialUI, TailwindCSS Bootstrap

SASS, SCSS

Styled Components

CSS modules

Web3.js, Truffle, Ganache

Figma, Photoshop, Adobe XD

Docker

REST API, GraphQL, Websockets.

Webpack

NPM/YARN

Jest, React testing library.

About

I have 3 years of experience in frontend development. Self- improved, every time improve my knowledge about used technologies and frameworks. I always try to pay attention to the details and nuances of the project and to find a good solution to the problem.

Work Experience

11.2022 - Present

Middle frontend developer Hivex

Developed features using Next.js, TanStackQuery, TS for the IT course platform (CMS)

03.2022 - 11.2022

Middle frontend developer Hivex

It was betting project. Worked on some features using React and wrote tests for them. Moreover, I restored the old feature and its functionality using Vue.js and Vuex. (These were lotteries for users). Studied the architecture of microfrontends.

06.2021 - 03.2022

Fullstack developer NIX

User can donate ETH Cryptocoin and get NFT. I used Solidity for smart-contracts on Backend and React with Web3.js on Frontend

08.2020 - 06.2021

Fullstack developer

Developing a Quizzes application in which in real-time an admin hosts questions in the room and the players can answers and get points. I was there as a full-stack developer and worked closely with many technologies on the frontend it was React, Typescript, Redux(Toolkit), WebSockets, TailwindCSS. Backend - NestJS, SocketIO, TypeORM, MySQL

Education History

Kharkiv National University of Radio Electronics

Bachelor degree at Computer Engineering English level - B2